Well, the immigration from the pastor of the first Christian church, Mr. Brand new butch
Let's pray
Father God, we love you. God, we're so grateful for how you've blessed us
God, I think everyone in this room loves Mayama, and that's a blessing
God, I pray that you would just be with every department, every board member
the mayor just everybody involved in how the city functions and operates and just grow their love for mayama make them more
passionate about it and that'll make this a better place and God will pray for the community as well
May we have a spirit of unity and progress as we move forward and continue to grow
So God be with this group tonight as they make decisions as they have updates and
Just may it be a positive night and another step forward for us
God, we love you. We pray that we'd be more like Jesus. Isn't that what we pray? Amen
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America and to the Republic for which it stands
One nation, another God, indivisible with liberty and justice for all
I think Brandon
But again put public input on scheduled personal appearances
Five discussion possible possible action on five a claims list
Motion to approve
All right
Five B claim to list for advance auto group
Motion to approve second
Parker abstain 5c minutes from the February 17th 2026 regular meeting must you approve?
All right
Minutes from the February 24th of 2026 regular meeting must you approve?
Six other new business if any which is residence and supposed to this agenda
Seven staffers ports
Eight trustee community announcements
Now and trust manager communications
10 this meeting will be continued from the council chambers recommending the staff room for the purpose of the executive session the completion of the regular meeting of the
MIPF a meeting